teefury.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy – TeeFury

At teefury you can rest assured that your personal information will never be rented, sold, or otherwise shared with any third party. Of course, this excludes the sharing of your shipping address with one of our shipping providers, UPS, FedEx, or USPS, in order to ship you your shirt. This also excludes the transmitting of your credit card information (fully encrypted) to our credit card processor, Authorize.net, in order to process your payment. These two exceptions are completely normal and necessary for any transaction to take place on any website where a physical product is being sold. In addition, we will never include you on any email newsletter unless you have elected to receive it, nor do we record or store any of your friends’ email addresses that are entered into our “Tell a Friend” fields. What we are trying to say is, your information is safe with us.

To find out more about teeFury, please go to our service section, or you can contact us here.

Also, we highly recommend checking out Today's Tee before it's gone!

Thanks for stopping by!

  * 1.

Introduction

  * 1.1

Tee Fury respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes what information Tee Fury collects about you during your visit to the Tee Fury website and what Tee Fury does with that information.

  * 1.2

Your visit to the Tee Fury website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Thus, by using this website, you are consenting to Tee Fury’s collection, storage, and use of your information as set out in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that Tee Fury not collect any information from you, please do not provide us with any such information. You must review this Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, just ask.

  * 1.3

Tee Fury may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. If Tee Fury changes this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As Tee Fury may make changes at any time without notifying you, Tee Fury suggests that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy.

  * 2.

Information That Tee Fury Collects

  * 2.1

Tee Fury collects and stores personal information. Personal information means personally identifiable information, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, Facebook account information, and other financial information.

  * 2.2

Tee Fury also collects and stores non-personal information. Non-personal information includes your browser type, your internet service provider and its location, the URL of the previous website you visited, your operating system, your IP address, and the date and time you accessed the Tee Fury website.

  * 3.

How and When Tee Fury Collects Information

  * 3.1

If you communicate with Tee Fury, Tee Fury may collect and store any information that you provide to us in any such communication. This information may include, for instance, your username on the Tee Fury website and your email address. Tee Fury does not store any email address that is entered into a “Tell a Friend” field.

  * 3.2

Tee Fury also collects personal information when you provide it in connection with a request for a product, service, or information. For example, if you create an account on the Tee Fury website, Tee Fury will collect your email address and a username that you create. If you order a t-shirt from Tee Fury, Tee Fury may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date, and email address. If you submit a design to Tee Fury, Tee Fury may collect your name, tax identification number, mailing address, email address, PayPal account information, other registration information, and questionnaire responses regarding your design. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, Tee Fury will collect your email address.

  * 3.3

Tee Fury allows you to sign in to the Tee Fury website using a Facebook account. Facebook sign-on features may also enable you to create an account more easily by prepopulating Tee Fury’s registration form with the information you provided to the social networking site. Typically, the first time you use Facebook, Facebook will inform you of the information that will be shared with Tee Fury. Tee Fury may use that information for purposes described in this Privacy Policy. To learn more about what information Facebook collects when you use it to sign into the Tee Fury website, please refer to Facebook’s privacy policy.

  * 3.4

Tee Fury uses analytic and reporting technologies to record non-personal information. Tee Fury may also use web beacons and cookies to collect your non-personal information. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than a 1x1 pixel that is placed on a web page or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the website or receiving the e-mail. Cookies and web beacons used by Tee Fury are not linked to personal information.

  * 4.

Uses

  * 4.1

Tee Fury primarily uses your personal information for processing, producing, and shipping the products that you order, administering Tee Fury forums, and providing customer service and support. For example, if you submit a design to Tee Fury, Tee Fury may use the information that you provide us to communicate with you and pay you any commissions that you earn. Similarly, if you sign up to receive Tee Fury newsletters, Tee Fury will use the email address you provide to send you the newsletters. Tee Fury does not share your credit card or other account information with unaffiliated third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities including, but not limited to, delivering a product or service that you order. Tee Fury may need to share certain personal information with third party vendors for reasons such as manufacturing, printing, or logistics. The personal information is not provided to these vendors for marketing purposes.

  * 4.2

Tee Fury primarily uses your non-personal information to help Tee Fury better understand how Tee Fury visitors use Tee Fury’s services and provide a better experience for our visitors.

  * 4.3

If you require help with Tee Fury services, a Tee Fury employee may ask you to confirm some of your private information, such as your name, delivery address, or other relevant identifying information. Tee Fury will never email you directly and ask for these details unless you have requested help or support.

  * 4.4

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal information frequently involves the transmission of data on an international basis. By providing Tee Fury with your personal information, you acknowledge and agree that Tee Fury may store your personal information and transfer it to and from our servers located in the United States and throughout the world.

  * 5.

Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

  * 5.1

Tee Fury does not share, rent, or trade your personal information with third parties for their marketing purposes.

  * 5.2

Tee Fury will disclose non-personal information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others. You may not opt-out of the sharing of this information. However, it cannot be easily used to identify you personally.

  * 5.3

Tee Fury reserves the right to disclose information, including personal information, to third party governmental agencies or third parties in order to comply with applicable laws, regulations, legal processes or governmental requests (such as in order to comply with a subpoena or court order), to protect Tee Fury’s rights, or to prevent, protect against, or investigate illegal activity such as credit fraud. For example, if you submit a design to Tee Fury, Tee Fury may disclose your information to a third party that alleges that you have infringed their intellectual property rights. Similarly, if you allege that an independent designer is infringing upon your intellectual property rights, we may disclose your information to that designer.

  * 5.4

Tee Fury contracts with several partners to help manage, monitor, and optimize Tee Fury’s business. For example, Tee Fury uses a third party to process credit card payments. Tee Fury also subcontracts with several shipping providers. Tee Fury may also subcontract out production, fulfillment, analytics, reporting, and/or other operations. Accordingly, Tee Fury may need to share personal information with these partners so that the partners can provide the services in question. Tee Fury will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such partners from disclosing your personal information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. Tee Fury cannot guarantee that such partners will not disclose your personal information.

  * 5.5

Tee Fury also uses third party vendors to display relevant ads for Tee Fury at locations away from the Tee Fury website on the Internet. These vendors may collect anonymous information about your visits to the Tee Fury website, and your interaction with our products and services. These vendors may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. Some of these vendors use cookies and/or web beacons to collect anonymous information and to display ads based on your previous visits to the Tee Fury site. You can opt out of interest-based advertising by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

  * 5.6

In the event Tee Fury goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or sale, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred to a successor-in-interest. Tee Fury reserves the right to transfer any personal and non-personal information to such successor-in-interest.

  * 6.

Children's Privacy

  * The Tee Fury website is intended for adults. Tee Fury does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. However, if the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us if they want this information deleted from our files so that it is not in retrievable form. If Tee Fury otherwise obtains knowledge that Tee Fury has personally identifiable information about a child under 13 in retrievable form in our files, Tee Fury will delete that information from our existing files so that it is not retrievable.

  * 7.

Security

  * 7.1

Tee Fury endeavors to protect all personal Information collected through the Tee Fury website in a safe, confidential, and secure manner.

  * 7.2

To this end, Tee Fury uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced security protocol that protects your credit card information and promotes secure online ordering. SSL Internet connections are encrypted, and may protect credit card ordering information, including your name, address, and credit card number, so it cannot be read in transit.

  * 7.3

Tee Fury also uses secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access to safeguard your personal information.

  * 8.

Reviewing and Making Changes to Personal Information

  * 8.1

You can obtain a copy of and request that we correct errors in your personal information by contacting us. For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity to obtain a copy of your personal information. If your personal information changes or if you no longer want to use Tee Fury services, you may correct or update your personal information and/or your account through the account management screen. If you would like to deactivate your account, you can contact us to request deactivation.

  * 8.2

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Tee Fury to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this privacy policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please contact us or write us:

Tee Fury LLC   
Attn. Legal – CA Privacy   
21098 Bake Parkway, Unit 100  
Lake Forest, CA, United States, 92630

  * 9.

Opting Out of Communications from Tee Fury

  * 9.1

Tee Fury wants to communicate with you via email only if you want to hear from us. When you purchase a t-shirt from Tee Fury, Tee Fury may from time to time send you email messages describing new products and offers. If, for any reason, you would no longer like to receive email messages from Tee Fury, you can unsubscribe by clicking the Unsubscribe button at the bottom of one of those emails.

  * 9.2

Your privacy is important to us, and for this reason we will never share or sell your email address with any third parties for direct marketing purposes. Please note, if you decide not to receive marketing emails from Tee Fury, you may still receive “Transactional” email messages regarding your order (i.e. order confirmation, shipping information, customer service notifications, etc.). If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at legal@teefury.com.

    * 10.

Waiver of Liability

    * 10.1

Whenever we obtain your personal information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. Nevertheless, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Accordingly, Tee Fury assumes no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access, or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

    * 10.2

The content that you store, post, or transmit on or through the Tee Fury website, such as forum postings and t-shirt designs, may be accessed by other users, including people that you do not know. We are not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your personal information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private.

    * 11.

Cookies Used

    * 11.1

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).  
_shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits  
_shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.  
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.  
_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional  
storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

          * Conclusion

          * If you have any other comments or queries about our privacy policy or the way we collect and use your information please ask.

  *
